hackett.co.uk 2013-05-05

# Privacy Policy | Hackett

Hackett is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to its Web Site. HACKETT analyses aggregate and non-personally identifiable data relating to usage of the Web Site. In accordance with UK data protection legislation, any personal information collected is done so with the knowledge and authorisation of users upon registration, request or submission to the Web Site. Information provided at the time of registration or submission will be used to provide the requested information and may be used for marketing statistical relating to HACKETT. It will not be used for any unsolicited communication to users unless so authorised by them. HACKETT will use its best endeavours to ensure that such data is kept secure at all times.

Moreover Hackett may also occasionally sell, rent or otherwise make available any personal data submitted by visitors to its Website to other carefully selected third-parties unless not required to do so by law and not authorised by visitors. Upon request, HACKETT will stop processing your personal information for marketing purposes. Furthermore, upon request, registered visitors may access and/or correct any erroneous information. 

Any request concerning personal data should be e-mailed to privacy@hackett.com.

We trust our privacy policy demonstrates our commitment to protecting your privacy.

For more information about our online shop, please read the the Online Shop [Terms Of Purchase, Privacy Policy](http://www.hackett.com/terms-purchase#terms8).
